Guide to the Burr McIntosh Photograph Collection 1898-1910 PR 41
New-York Historical Society
Burr McIntosh photograph collection
1898-1910
New-York Historical Society
McIntosh, Burr, 1862-1942
PR 41
5.67 Linear feet (17 boxes)
Collection of photographs, mainly celebrity portraits, taken by Burr McIntosh. The Burr McIntosh Photograph Collection is digitized and available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the New York Herald Tribune, July 1, 1942.
Access Restrictions
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Biographical Note
Burr McIntosh had an eclectic career. He was known, at different points in his life, to be a lecturer, photographer, movie studio owner, actor, author, publisher, reporter and a pioneer in the early movie and radio business. While many of these endeavors were short-lived, they gained him prestige and popularity among the stylish set.
He was born William McIntosh August 21, 1862, in Wellsville, Ohio, and attended Lafayette College, 1880 - 82, and Princeton, 1882 - 83. After Princeton, McIntosh was in the coal business in Pittsburgh for a brief time and then followed this up with a short stint as a reporter for the Philadelphia News. He came to New York and made his theatrical debut in Bartley Campbell's "Paquita" in August 31, 1885, beginning his most successful and memorable career, as an actor on the theatrical stage. He adopted a stage name at this time, changing his first name to Burr. His biggest success came playing the character Talbot "Taffy" Wynne in the original 1895 Broadway production of "Trilby" at the Garden Theatre. He repeated this performance in major Broadway revivals in 1905 and 1915, as well as in a production in London at His Majesty's Theatre. McIntosh also appeared in a number of Augustus Thomas' plays, beginning with "Arizona" and "In Mizzoura."
In 1898, Burr McIntosh went to Cuba to cover the Spanish-American War for Leslie's Weekly as a reporter and photographer. Defying orders forbidding any newspapermen to land in Cuba until every soldier in the Army had landed, he jumped over the side of a boat and swam to shore in time to get the only photographs of the troops coming ashore at Daiquiri. In Cuba, he became ill with "yellow jack" (a form of yellow fever) and was out of action. He eventually recovered and wrote of his exploits in a 1901 book, What Little I Saw of Cuba.
The year 1901 also saw the establishment of his first photographic studio on West 33rd Street, conveniently located across from the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, a meeting place of many of the society and theatrical people whose portraits would be taken by the studio. This work led McIntosh to found the Burr McIntosh Monthly, which ran from 1903 to 1910, and offered portraits of theater idols, scenes at fashionable athletic events, picturesque genre and nature studies, and discussions of photography as art. In 1908, McIntosh declared bankruptcy and ceased publishing in May 1910.
In addition to acting and publishing, Burr McIntosh accompanied Secretary of War William H. Taft's 1905 peace trip to the Philippines as the official photographer.
In 1910, Burr McIntosh announced an elaborate plan to found an artists' colony with the fortune he hoped to make from the early movie industry. To accomplish this goal, he moved to California to organize his own film company. He also announced his retirement from the stage after his 1909 national tour in "The Gentleman from Mississippi." This retirement was not permanent as McIntosh appeared on Broadway six more times between 1914 and his last play, "Robert E. Lee," in 1923, including his successful revival of Taffy in "Trilby" in 1915. Neither the fortune from the movie industry nor the artists' colony ever materialized. His movie career began in 1914 recreating his stage performance in "In Mizzoura." The following year he starred in the title role of the movie " Colonel Carter of Cartersville," which was the only film that he ever produced. His work as an actor in movies stretched from the silent movies of 1914 until the era of sound movies, ending with "The Richest Girl in the World" in 1934.
McIntosh took time away from movies during the First World War when he lectured on patriotism and the role of the United States in the war at venues around the country, including the Metropolitan Opera House and Carnegie Hall in New York. He also entertained as a YMCA worker in army camps in France and Germany. After the war, he supported Leonard Wood for the Republican presidential nomination with further speaking appearances.
In the disastrous year of 1929, Burr McIntosh declared bankruptcy. His wife, the former Jean Snowden of Saratoga, whom he had married in New York in 1914, attempted suicide. According to an interview that McIntosh gave to the New York Times at this time, she had succumbed to her serious disappointment that McIntosh's work in Hollywood had not produced the financial returns they had anticipated.
From 1930 until his death in Los Angeles on April 28, 1942, Burr McIntosh was known as the "Cheerful Philosopher" as the host of a radio programs and in a series of lectures offering optimistic views on life. He had one daughter, Nancy McIntosh.
Scope and Content Note
The Burr McIntosh Photograph Collection spans the period from ca. 1900 to 1910 and documents McIntosh's career as a photographer of prominent figures in the arts, society, and politics, many of whom were his friends and acquaintances. The vast majority of the ca. 3,000 prints were made by the New-York Historical Society in the late 1940s from glass plate negatives taken during the period 1900 - 1910; the negatives were destroyed after being printed. The remaining glass plates, approximately 600, do not have prints.
The collection consists of early work such as images from the Spanish-American War siege of Santiago, Cuba, which he covered for Leslie's Weekly and published in The Little I Saw of Cuba. Another group of photos shows Secretary Taft's good will trip to the Philippines in 1905. Most of the remaining images are society and celebrity portraits, many of which were published in McIntosh's magazine. Actors Ethel and John Barrymore appear at the seashore; philanthropist A. G. Vanderbilt celebrates a holiday at his Adirondack lodge; ingenue Evelyn Nesbit poses seductively; and architect Charles F. McKim enjoys a quiet country outing. Children playing, professional New York theatrical groups, and miscellaneous buildings are also included in the collection. Society sporting gatherings such as horse shows and events, including polo and fox hunting, and sailing at Newport, Rhode Island, are also well represented within the collection.
Identification of the sitter is from the original caption information on the glass plate negatives, usually limited to the sitter's name that, in some cases, is only a surname. The unidentified portraits in all the series include many theatrical, costumed portraits of men, women, and groups. Most of the sitters appear in more than one series.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into four series:
Series I. 8 x 10 inch Prints
Series II. 5 x 7 inch Prints
Series III. 11 x 14 inch Prints
Series IV. Glass Plate Negatives
Thereunder, photographs are filed alphabetically by sitter.
Related Material at the Department of Prints, Photographs, and Architectural Collections
A full run of volumes of Burr McIntosh Monthly is available in the New-York Historical Society library, as well as a copy of Burr McIntosh's The Little I Saw of Cuba. The Theatrical Portrait File (PR 104) contains several cabinet cards from Burr McIntosh's studio which were given to N-YHS by other donors.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital copies are available in the Shelby White and Leon Levy Digital Library.
Glass negatives.; negatives (photographs); Photographic prints.; Buildings -- United States.; Celebrities -- United States -- Portraits.; Children playing.; Documentary photography.; Dwellings -- New York (State) -- Adirondack Mountains.; Socialites -- United States -- Portraits.; Spanish-American War, 1898.; Theatrical companies -- Portraits.; Asia -- Description and travel.; Santiago de Cuba (Cuba); United States -- Foreign relations -- Japan.; United States -- Foreign relations -- Philippines.; Barrymore, Ethel, 1879-1959 -- Portraits.; Barrymore, John, 1882-1942 -- Portraits.; Caruso, Enrico, 1873-1921 -- Portraits.; Langtry, Lillie, 1853-1929 -- Portraits.; Longworth, Alice Roosevelt, 1884-1980 -- Portraits.; McIntosh, Burr, 1862-1942; McKim, Charles Follen, 1847-1909 -- Portraits.; Nesbit, Evelyn, 1884-1967 -- Portraits.; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930 -- Portraits.; Tarkington, Booth, 1869-1946 -- Portraits.; Tesla, Nikola, 1856-1943 -- Portraits.; Vanderbilt, Alfred Gwynne, 1877-1915 -- Portraits.
- Series I. 8 x 10 inch prints, ca. 1900 - 1910
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of prints arranged in three subseries: Portraits, filed alphabetically by sitter; Subjects, filed alphabetically; and Unidentified Portraits, divided into children, men, and women. The portraits contain many of the men and women of society and the theater community who figured in Burr McIntosh's magazine, including Ethel Barrymore, actress Clara Bloodgood, W. Gould Brokaw (including his home Nirvana in Great Neck, Long Island), Marie Dressler, Robert Edeson, Bijou Fernandez, Edna Wallace Hopper, Joseph Jefferson, Lillie Langtry, Burr McIntosh himself, Evelyn Nesbit, Charles Richman, as well as prints of an unidentified Vanderbilt ball and the Alfred G. Vanderbilt's residence in the Adirondacks. A significant group within the subject subseries consists of photographs of many American buildings, both named and unidentified, interiors and exteriors, private homes and resorts. There is also a large selection of prints of the Taft trip to the Philippines. There are school photos of groups of students generally consisting of music or sports groups posed either on a school field or on the steps of a school building, such as from private schools as the Hackley School at Tarrytown in its first few years of operation. The remaining miscellaneous subjects are the usual as throughout the entire collection, focusing on naval and sailing ships, horse shows, theater companies, and Cuba during the Spanish American War. The subseries of unidentified portraits are divided into children, men, and, the largest category, women, many of whom appear to be theatrical.
  There is a single print of each sitter or subject unless otherwise noted.
  - PORTRAITS
    - Adams, Maude (5) Addington, W. L. Adler, Jacob Alexander, Mrs. F. P. Ali, George Allen, Viola (6) Ames, Knowlton Arbuckle, Mrs. John (3) Arthur, Paul (2) Atwater, Mrs. E. S. (5) Ayre, Mrs. H. E. (Offsite-box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bagge, Mrs. N. A. Baise, Willard Baldwin, Carol (2) Barrymore, Ethel (24) Barrymore, John (3) Barrymore, Lionel Barrymore, Ethel and John (4) Barstow, Mrs. L. G. Bates, Blanche Bates, J.J. Bellew, Kryle (4) Benet, Mrs. E. T. Benridge, Ray (2) Bentley, Irene (12) Bergere, Valerie (2) Berry, Mrs. B. J. Beulah Beverly, Mrs. Mitchell (Offsite-box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bingham, Amilia (8) Birrell, Mrs. A. (2) Black, Mrs. John C. Blackburn, Vivian (w/ group) Blair, E. (3) Blanchard, Mrs. H. E. Blanchard, W. W. Block, Harry Bogue, Virginia (2) Bonnell, William F. Booth Bostwick, Mrs. A. C. Breckenridge, John Breckenridge, T. C. Briggs, M. (2) Brokaw (3) Brokaw, W. Gould (3) Brokaw, W. Gould - residence (2) Burke, Billie (2) Burt, Laura Bustanby (2) (Offsite-box 1, Folder 3)
    - Calve, Emma (2) Cameron, Grace (3) Campbell, Mrs. B. R. Carlisle, Sibyl Carroll, J. W. Carter, Ernest (2) Carter, Mrs. R. R. Chadwick, George B. (2) Chalfort, Eleanor Chapman, J. D. Chase, Pauline (2) Cheney, Mrs. Vance (3) Childs, Otis H. Chittendon, Dr. A. Christy, Mrs. H. C. Clare, Mrs. E. L. Clark wedding bridesmaids Clark, Mrs. G. W. Clark, Thomas G. Colby, Bainbridge Comstock, Nannette (3) Conness, Robert (2) Conquest, Ida Corbin, Mrs. W. H. Corson, Mrs. Courtleigh, William Crane, W. H. company Cranier, Mrs. H. C. Creighton, Madge Creykendall, Ursula (Offsite-box 1, Folder 4)
    - Daly, Mrs. J W. David, W. B. (2) Davis (8) De Angelis, Jefferson (3) DePew, Chauncey M. (Chauncey Mitchell) (3) DePew, Mrs. Chauncey (5) De Sousa, May (2) DeWitt, John R. (2) De Wolf, Drina (2) Dodson, Mr. and Mrs. J. E. (14) Donaldson, Mrs. Drew Donner, Mr. P. R. Doro, Marie (9) Dressler, Marie (7) Duke, Miss M. (2) Dulles, Miss E. (2) Dumont, Santos (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
    - Easton, Judge Earl, Virginia (5) Eastland, Mrs. L. B. (2) Edeson, Robert (8) Elkins, Miss (2) Elkins Jr., L. B. Elliot Gertrude (2) Embry, M. V. Eustis, Jennie Everett, Col. S. E. (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
    - Fahnstock, Mr. (3) Fahnstock, Mrs. Fallows (4) Farnham, Mrs. Paulding Farnham statues (4) Farrington, Nina (2) Ferguson, William (3) Fernandez, Bijou (7) Finlay, Miss. G. (4) Firth, Elizabeth Fisher, Alice Fitch, Clyde (3) Fitzhugh, Anna Fleischman, Mrs. W. M. Florence, Miss. K. (3) Flower, Mrs. K. S. Follett, Maizie (2) Foster, Mrs. A. L. Frear, T. Fritz, Mrs. J. E. Frontman, Fay Fuller, Mrs. J. E. (Offsite-box 2, Folder 7)
    - Gaines (5) Gardner, Mrs. A. P. Gardner, Dr. John H. Garfield, H. S. Gascoigne, Miss M. George, Grace (10) Geraghty Gibney, Dr. V. Gibson, Mrs. Gibson, Dessa Giffen, Mrs. John Gilbert, Mrs. George W. (3) Gillette, Mrs. Charles W. Gillette, Mrs. John Gillette, William (5) Glaser, Lulu (2) Golden, Bernice (3) Goncouria, Ada Gonning, Miss Goodwin, Nat C. (3) Gordore, D. E. Graham, Miss (3) Grant, Miss Granville, Mrs. C. G. (2) Green, Daisy (5) Gruss, Charles E. Guardavarri Gunning, Louise (Offsite-box 2, Folder 8)
    - Hackett, James K. (2) Haine, Mrs. G. G. Hale, Helen Hale, Walter (2) Halito, Mrs. Arthur Hall, Lewis A. (3) Hamilton, Mrs. E. C. Hamilton, Mrs. M. S. (2) Hamlin, Conde Hanna (2) Hanna, child Har (?), A. E. Hardin Jr, Mrs. E. L. (2) Harper, Belle (5) Harris, child (4) Hart, W. S. (3) Havemeyer, Mrs. H. H. Havemeyer, M. (2) Hayman, Mrs. Alfred (Offsite-box 2, Folder 9)
    - Hegeman, Virginia (2) Held, Anna Hendrix, W. G. (4) Hewlett, Mr. Hickman, A. Hickschic, Mrs. A. A. Hoagland, group Hobson, Maude (2) Hogarti Holland, Joseph (3) Hooper Hope, Lady Hopper, Edna Wallace (9) Houseman, Edith (2) Houston, Mrs. W. C. Hoyt, Mrs. Hubbard, Elbert and group Huber, Mrs. J. B. Huber, Mrs. V. S. Hudson wedding bridesmaid Huntington, Mrs. A. J. Huntley, G. P. Hume, Judge (2) Huyler, John S. Hyem, Constance (Offsite-box 2, Folder 10)
    - Ingalls, Gladys (2) Irwin, May (Offsite-box 3, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Maude B. (2) James, Mrs. V. F. Jay, Col. William (2) Jefferson, Joseph (11) Jeffreys, Elsie (7) Jennings, E. H. Johnson, Mrs. W. Martin (2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 12)
    - Kahn, Florence Keen, Mrs. Wilson Keldy, Herbert Kierney, James (2) Kouatze, B. C. (2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 13)
    - Langtry, Lillie (7) Lathrop, Frank F., group Leiter, Mr. J. Leonard, Imogene (2) Leonard, Mrs. T. E. Lessi, Leah (2) Lessing, Madge (3) Libby, William H. (2) Ling, Ritchie Litt, Mrs. Jacob (2) Lounsbury, children Lounsbury, Mrs Lounsbury, Edith Lounsbury, Mrs. Richard (Offsite-box 3, Folder 14)
    - McBirney, Mrs. Day (2) McClellan McDonald, Christy (4) McFarland, Dr. W. L. MacGinn, Bonnie (8) McGaffrey, Dominick McIntosh, Burr (11) Mack, Andrew Mackenzie, M. (3) Mackay family (2) McKim family (4) McKim, C. F. MacLaren, Miss S. S. McLean, Mrs. E. W. McVickers, Noel (3) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 15)
    - Magowan, Gov. Maini Jr., A. W. (2) Manuel Marlowe, Julia Martin (2) Mason automobile Mason, Delia (5) Masterson, Mrs. W. J. (2) Mathey, Dean Maxwell, T. (2) Mengis, Mr. C. E. Meyer wedding Millinres, Mme Mills, Frankie Moffat Montgomery, W. H. Moore, Miss (2) Moore, Mr. Moore, Olive Celeste Morgan, Mr. and Mrs. G. D. (3) Morrison, J. (2) Morton, Paul (2) Mosher, Mrs. B. B. Munn, Dr. D. Murdock, Mrs. S. J., and children Murray, Kenneth (4) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 16)
    - Nash, Mary (2) Neilson, Miss C. Nesbit, Evelyn (5) Nevins, A. P. Noyes, J. W. Noyes, Clara J. (2) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 17)
    - Oatman, E. E. Odell, Estelle Oliver, Mrs. Henry Opp, Julie (8) Osborn, Mrs. Robert Osborne (3) Otis, Mrs. E. P. (3) (Offsite-box 3, Folder 18)
    - Parker, Olive Parr family (3) Passow, Capt. Peats, Alfred and family (7) Peck Pennowyer, Miss (2) Peplow's studio Petit, Mme. E. (12) Phillips, Phylis Pogue, Mrs. Saul F. Potter Jr., Mrs. E. M. (2) Power, Tyrone (2) Presley Proctor, Katherine (Offsite-box 4, Folder 19)
    - Radford, Mrs. (3) Radford, Miss B. Rainsford, Mr. R. E. Ray, Col. Frank (4) Ray, Robert Remsen (3) Reynolds Reynolds, Mrs. William H. and children Rhodes, Mrs. R. R. (2) Rice, Rev. W. H. Richman, Charles (11) Richman, Mrs. Charles (2) Ricker, Mrs. A. P. Ring, Blanche (2) Ring, Florence Ritchie, Adele (19) Robinson, Mrs. Robinson, D. T. L. Robinson, Elsie Robson (Belmont), Eleanor (9) Roosevelt, Theodore Roseberry, Augusta C. Rowan, Miss Lansing (2) Ryan, Elsa (3) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 20)
    - Sayers, Margaret Schoen, Charles (2) Seligman family Seygard, Mme. Camille (3) Sharp, Claudine (2) Shayne, Edith Sheldon, Suzanne Shillier, William Smith, Proctor Smith, R. A. (4) Snyder, Mrs. J. E. Sore, Mrs. Paul O. (4) Southwick, Laurence (3) Sperry (2) Spong, Hilda Starback family Stevens, Francis Stewart, Mrs. J. A. Stewart, Mrs. M. Gladstone (2) Stokes, Mrs. T. D. Stuart, Mrs. E. M. (2) Stuart, William (2) Surratt, Valesca (2) Swann (2) Swann, Lady (3) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 21)
    - Taintor, F. V. (2) Tarrant, Mrs. W. T. Tennant, Dorothy (Lady Dorothy Stanley) (2) Thesis, Josephine Three Little Maids Co. (4) Tial, Ben Tiffany, Charles L., residence Tod, Mrs. J. Kennedy (3) Tod, Mrs. Robert L. Truax, Sarah (4) Truesdale, Mrs. W. H. Z. (3) Truesdale, William Haynes Truey, Miss L. Tynan, B. (5) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 22)
    - Ulrich, Olive (Offsite-box 4, Folder 23)
    - Vanbrough, Irene Van Buren Van Buren, Mary Vanderbilt ball (unidentified) (8) Vanderbilt residence (Alfred G. Vanderbilt) - Adirondacks (11) Van Riper, Mrs. E. V. (Offsite-box 4, Folder 24)
    - Waldegram, Lilias (3) Webb, N. (3) Weir, Mrs. D. L. Whiting, Jean (6) Whitney, A. E. Whitney, Mrs. Warren Wilson, Edith Wilson, Miss F. N. (2) Wilson, Francis (2) Wilson, Harry R. (2) Woodruff, Harry (3) Woodward, George (3) Wooley (3) Wynne, Bessie (8) (Offsite-box 4, Folder 25)
    - Yerkes, Mabel (2) Young, Mrs. Redd Johnson (Offsite-box 4, Folder 26)
  - SUBJECTS
    - Automobiles (4) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 27)
    - Cuba (39) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 28)
    - Buildings, identified (61) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 29)
    - Buildings, unidentified (43) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 30)
    - Naval ships (22) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 31)
    - Newport Naval Training Station (8) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 32)
    - Newport, Rhode Island, sailing ships (6) (Offsite-box 5, Folder 33)
    - Polo and horse shows (21) - including Orange County Hunts (The Plains, VA), Van Cortlandt Polo Park (Bronx, NY), Westchester Polo Club Grounds (Newport, RI) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 34)
    - School groups (16) - Hackley School (Tarrytown, NY), St. Paul School (Garden City, NY) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 35)
    - Taft trip (92) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 36 - 37)
    - Theater companies (12), including Puff Puff, Woodland, Other Girl. (Offsite-box 6, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous subjects (14) (Offsite-box 6, Folder 39)
  - UNIDENTIFIED PORTRAITS
    - Children (35) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 40)
    - Men (52) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 41)
    - Women (192) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 42)
    - Women (192) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 43)
    - Women (192) (Offsite-box 7, Folder 44)
- Series II. 5 x 7 Prints, ca. 1900 - 1910
  Series II. 5 x 7 Inch Prints consists of prints divided into three subseries: Portraits, filed alphabetically by sitter; Subjects, filed alphabetically; and Unidentified Portraits, divided into children, groups, men, and women. The portraits represent the content of Burr McIntosh's monthly magazine, concentrating on society people and many performers, such as animal impersonator George Ali, Ethel Barrymore, Mrs. Patrick Campbell, and Enrico Caruso. This series has fewer subject prints than the others, predominantly consisting of those from horse shows and the Taft trip to the Philippines.
  - PORTRAITS
    - Abarbanell, Lina (3) Abbott, Mrs. Austin Adams, T. S. Ainsley, Mrs. W. A. Alexander, Douglas (4) Alexander, J. H. (2) Ali, George (3) Allen, Rosamund (3) Allward, Mrs. H. (2) Anthony, C. D. Anthony, Ethel (4) Atherton, G. F. (2) Atwater, E. S. (2) Atwater, Mrs. E. S. Atwater, F. C. Averill, Mrs Elizabeth Bacon, Roy (3) Baker, Mrs. C. D. Baldwin, William (2) Ballentine, C. M. (3) Ballentine, Mrs. George A. (6) Banfield, Gerard Barker, Major G. M. (9) Barker, Dr. P. M. (4) Barry, Richard Barrymore, Ethel (23) Barstow, Mrs. W. A. Bell, Miss C. B. (4) Benedict, Walter St. John Berkeley, Arthur (5) Berry, Charles K. Berry, Evelyn (3) Betts, G. W. (2) Black, John C. (3) Blanchard, Ethel Blanchard, Mrs. H. E. Blanchard, Maude (2) Blanchard, R. L. (4) Blanchard, W. W. Blass, Mr. Bond, Mr. H. L. Bostwick, Mrs. A. C. (2) Bowne, Miss Marjory (5) Boyd, A. C. Brady, Dr. C. T. (4) Brady, E. B. (2) Brantingham, Mrs. C. H. (2) Brevort, W. H. (3) Brevort, Mrs. W. H. (2) Briggs, M. Britton, W. (2) Brooks Stanley Brown, Capt. (2) Brown, Mr. Harrison Brown, J. J. (2) Brown, Mrs. Vernon (2) Browning (2) Bull, Miss (3) Butler, C. R. (2) Calvert, M. P. (2) Cameron, Alex (2) Campanari, Mr. (2) Campbell, Mrs. Patrick (4) Campbell, W. H. Carew, Mrs. C. J. Carew, R. Borden (2) Carnegie Carnegie, F. F. (2) Carr, Louise (3) Carroll, G. M. (2) Caruso, Enrico (10) Chadwick, George B. (6) Chalfont, Eleanor (4) Chambers (2) Chambers, Mrs. Robert W. (2) Chandler, Mrs. Chandler, Peter R. Chapman, Mrs. J. Chapman, F. D. Cheatham, Kitty (3) Cheney, Mrs. J. B. Chester, George Randolph (6) Clark, Mrs. F. Ambrose (2) Clark, Mrs. G. G. Clark, Mrs. Robert J. Clark, W. Clarkson, Mrs. A. C. (2) Clayton, Mrs. A. P. Clifford, Evelyn (2) Clyde, Mrs. W. P. Cochron, Gifford A. Coddington, P. M. (2) Coe, George V. Cogkendall, Mrs. R. B. (2) Cole, Mrs. V. T. Colgate, Florence (3) Colgate, Mabel (3) Colgate, S. S. (3) Colgate, Mrs. S. S. (2) Comstock, Mr. C. A. Comstock, Nannette (2) Conger (2) Cook, Robert S. (2) Copens (4) Corbin, Mrs. W. H. Corgin, Lt. E. L. Cornwell (2) Condert, Renee Countz, Miss B. C. Coxcaden, J. S. (2) Crandell, Dr. R. P. Crane, F. G. (2) Crosby, Mrs. Southgate Custis, L. V. Cuthel (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)